This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
sets sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hat crew,
Luffy struggled in vain to rescue his brother from execution at the hands of the Navy.
In the end, both Ace and the legendary pirate Whitebeard lost their lives in the conflict.
As for Whitebeard and Ace, I'm sure you won't object to their friends taking care of the burial.
I'll allow it, Shanks. Just this once.
But why?
Let me take responsibility.
Thank you.
Now go treat the engine before it's too late!
This war is over!
The Navy has won!
Hurrah!
Mighty leaders face each other down!
Heralding the new era!
Repeat, this is Navy headquarters regarding the battle.
Heralding the new war.
Although Whitebeard's new allies made the conflict a long and ardent event.
Struggled nicely in the name of the war.
We are pleased to report that our victory will be absolute,
and the execution of what is the end of the paradise.
What are they saying? I can't make anything out!
I know. The connection must be bad.
What happened in the war? Did the Navy win or did the pirates?
Sure are leaving us hanging, huh?
Is there a way to repair it?
Shhh! Sounds like it's clearing up.
The Whitebeard pirates were defeated?
That means the good guys won, right?
Repeat, this is Navy headquarters with an update regarding the battle at Marineford.
Although Whitebeard and his allies made the conflict a long and arduous affair,
the Marines struggled violently in the name of justice.
We are pleased to report that our victory over Whitebeard was absolute,
and the execution of Portugus D. Ace was carried out.
You are once again safe from the treachery of pirates,
thanks to the Navy and world government's efforts.
We did it!
We're invincible!
No attempt at the power of the Navy!
Just you wait! Some day they'll summon me to serve at HQ and I'll be ready!
Thank goodness the war is finally over!
Alright!
I thought it never ends!
Whitebeard's reign of terror is over! Party time!
The good guys beat the bad ones, right, Mom?
That's right! And we have the Navy to thank!
I knew they could do it!
Be sad, pirates!
I thought we were goners!
Now three chairs!
Yeah!
One for the world government!
One for the admirals!
And a big one for all the Marines!
Yeah!
Back at Marineford and far away from celebrations of the Navy victory, there are seven ships afloat.
Those who will soon take part in the new pirate era are witnessing one of the great turning points in history.
Ever mindful of the Navy's ruthless sense of justice, they still stare upon the aftermath of war, knowing the ensuing chaos will leave plenty of opportunity for new powers to arise.
Captain Drake, sir.
At last.
The war's over.
Both sides are weakened.
The Navy and the pirates.
It's just a matter of time.
Whitebeard's territory.
Other pirates will be vying for control.
It's bound to get pretty rough.
Now.
Blackbeard's reign has begun.
Not only has he built a formidable crew, but he's got two devil fruit powers.
Just our luck.
It's gonna be a while before we've got the strength to topple those guys.
It's all his fault.
Damn that Blackbeard.
I'll find him and make him pay.
Alright!
Let's go!
Yeah!
What the hell is going on?
What are you talking about, Captain?
Is something wrong?
Trafalgar Law is no friend of Straw Hat.
Why is he saving him now?
What's the catch?
Huh?
Law has got a reputation.
He's one of the North Blue's most brutal pirates.
There's no way he'd have saved him unless he was expecting something back in return.
How odd.
Captain Hawkins, what seems to be the matter?
I've been trying to determine if Straw Hat Luffy is alive or dead, but the cards won't say.
To tell you the truth, this war had me pretty worked up at first. Never thought the Great Whitebeard would die.
Well, either way, it's over.
Yeah, guess so.
Nothing's ever over.
One old bastard kicks the bucket and an even meaner one takes his place.
Blackbeard's gonna turn everything upside down.
See ya!
See before, the four emperors ran the new world.
Whitebeard, Kaido, Big Mom, and Shanks.
But now that Whitebeard is dead, everything is out of balance and no one knows how the scales are gonna tip.
It's a brand new hour.
Like none before.
And it's ours for the taking.
News of the Navy's victory in the war at Marineford,
toward the deadliest battles since the dawn of the great pirate era spread like
wildfire and people across the world are celebrating the good news the east blue
the west blue
we can finally sail in peace raise your glasses the south blue celebratory sail over here
over here too get your body food i don't have a care in the world the north blue
oh man that really hit the spot keep the drinks coming next round is on the house the grand line
can we join the navy too i'm gonna beat all the pirates i am yeah right thank you and may this
peace last as it goes with history the passage of time distorts facts and glosses over imported
details soon the only two words that stand out are navy victory lost in the celebration most
people fail to consider the war's real consequences what was that
you're all fools didn't you hear him the one piece white beard said it's real
so gold roger wasn't lying after all well guess we better get to finding it
enough wasting away in this dump time to set sail
though navy victory might have a nice ring to it it does not necessarily equate to peace
you guys aren't welcome here get out of our town
for white beard was a pirate but he was also a protector and news of his death emboldened pirates
who previously cowered from him
fleet admiral sengoku
i'm very sorry for the intrusion sir but we've just received urgent news from impel down should i
continue sir magellan is he all right he was beaten badly and is barely alive the medical team has
been working on his injuries non-stop but magellan is ashamed and he's blaming himself for what happened
down there if his wounds weren't so severe then he'd probably be at risk of killing himself don't tell
me that nonsense he knows how much we need him yes sir of course what exactly did happen that impel
down things there are quite disastrous the situation on level six is especially dire it's a crisis
elaborate
uh
what's wrong boys feeling a bit down thinking you'll be stuck in this hell hole forever
just wait until you die huh so how about this start fighting start fighting right there in your jail cell
those of you who survive get a free ticket to join my crew and sail out of here with me
this ain't for real it's time to play now who should i kill first
he had his pick of the deadliest criminals in the world and he had them fight to the death while he
simply stood there and watched yes but only four of the prisoners were taken san juan wolf avalo
pizarro bosco shot and katerina devin as you saw but i'm sorry to say sir that his new recruits aren't
the only prisoners who were missing from level six i
so impelled down is swimming with escaped criminals the worst the world has ever seen
we can't let a single one of them get away if they stole a ship and slipped into some country unnoticed
there's no telling what sort of terrible things might happen start a count of how many level six
prisoners are missing you have their names and put out a most wanted list as soon as possible
what's wrong well uh actually i'm under direct orders from the world government to keep this
matter a secret at any cost a huge blunder like this one could badly hurt the government's reputation
i don't give a damn
uh
oh
Doflamingo! You bastard!
Come on, lighten up. We both know you're too weak to be a warlord. Just face it!
I'll do you a favor for old time's sake. We won't say the government had you put down. We'll say you gave your life in battle.
So Sengoku put you up to this?
I'll tear him apart!
Think higher up the ladder.
It's too hard down here. I can't take it. Goodbye, cool world.
Shut the hell up, Beppo. I was doing fine till you said something.
I guess all that fur isn't much help, huh? Poor guy.
I hate going underwater. It gets so stuffy in this thing.
And the company down here is oppressive, too.
Yeah, well, right back at you, you jerk!
Such vitriol. What can a poor bear do?
To win the love of his fellow crew members!
Crash! I hate the smell!
Bad bear touch!
I made my wits in here!
We'll have to go up!
Even at least just a second, please!
Okay, let's go and we'll ask the captain to surface!
Everything will be fine!
Itchy!
It's her so freaking itchy!
What a nice breeze! I don't think I'm ever going back down!
Now, first the right cheek, then left. Oh, yeah. Perfect. Hi, Snake.
Snake!
What the hell?
Where did that thing come from?
Not good.
It looks like a Navy ship!
Hurry! Go tell Captain!
Quiet! Someone's up there!
It's a warlord, Boa Hancock the Pirate Empress!
Don't worry. I've turned all the Marines on board into stone.
So, what is Luffy's condition? Will he be all right?
Can I help somehow? Anything at all?
Gosh, I was afraid the Navy was still hot on our tail.
But I don't understand. How did you know the sub was going to surface right here and now?
I simply had Salome track your ship underwater.
Oh!
Don't change the subject! Luffy is all that matters!
You're right.
Really, dude?!
I beg of you, if he is hurt in any way, please let me know at once!
Oh! Captain!
I did everything I possibly could.
So does that mean that he'll be okay?
We'll just have to wait and see. He's in stable condition for now.
However, he took on a lot more damage than most could endure.
And there's no guarantee that he'll survive.
What an uplifting prognosis!
Who said that?!
Me, duh!
Anyhow, if you want Strawboy to wake up, you're gonna have to show him some love!
We owe him our lives, so take good care of him!
We should still be in prison without his help!
Now all the new Kama can finally go to the Kamabaka kingdom like we've always dreamed!
Off we go! Farewell, Straw Hat! We're heading home!
Yeah!
So, uh, who are they?
They are a group of prisoners from Impel Down.
It appears that Luffy is their friend.
They must have snuck onto the ship as well.
I can't believe he pushed his body past its limit a second time.
That's how strong the bond was between Strawboy and Aceboy.
You tell him, Eva! Nothing can stop him then and nothing will stop him now!
Right?
I wish that were so, but fate can be cruel.
You can't save everyone.
All of that work for nothing.
He's nearly dead because that's the kind of world this is!
Don't get down now, Eva! Straw Hat can pull through this! I know it!
You gotta live, Straw Hat! Don't you dare die on us!
Luffy has touched so many lives.
If only there was some way I could take his place so that he may survive.
Poor darling.
So lucky.
Must be nice having the pirate empress fawn over you like that.
Yeah, wow.
You're a new face.
Are you one of Strawboy's pals?
No.
I can't say why I saved him.
Or it's complicated at least.
Are you gonna pressure me for the details?
No, no.
Let's just say that your heart guided you to his side.
Hey, wait!
You can't walk around, Hits!
Don't push your body like that!
Captain told you to rest, remember?
Your wound could open up!
Come back here, please!
Leave me be.
Jinbei!
I know you.
Captain Law from the North Blue.
You look awful.
Should you really be moving around like that?
I owe you.
I owe you my life.
Enough.
Lie down.
Hmm.
My mind is troubled.
Luffy!
The pain I feel for him is such that I can't rest.
I have failed you, friend.
Remorse.
If this is how I feel, then just imagine him.
His collapse may have been a mercy since it allowed us to take him away.
But what now?
I've failed you.
How awful.
Should you really be moving around like that?
I owe you.
I owe you my life.
Enough.
Lie down.
Hmm.
My mind is troubled.
Luffy!
The pain I feel for him is such that I can't rest.
I have failed you, friend.
Remorse.
If this is how I feel, then just imagine him.
His collapse may have been a mercy since it allowed us to take him away.
Okay, but what now?
Even if he survives with the immensity of his loss,
I fear for the moment he awakens.
You, the fuzzy one, where's your transponder snail?
Who, me?
I'll go get it, if you'd like.
No fair, I wish I got to serve the Empress too.
Mm-hmm.
I will summon the Kuja ship so we can sail across the Calm Belt,
even with this submarine.
The world government can't find out Luffy's alive,
or else they'll come after him.
Let us harbor him safely at the Maiden Island.
Really?
As long as they still view me as a warlord,
Luffy will not be in danger there.
Luffy.
Luffy is taken to Amazon Lily to hide from the Navy
At Hancock's order, Luffy is taken to Amazon Lily to hide from the Navy while he recovers.
Although Lore was able to tend to his injuries, when he awakens, Luffy is haunted by memories of the war and falls into deep despair.
On the next, One Piece, landing at the Maiden Island, the harsh reality falls upon Luffy.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!